var questionArray = [
  {
    question:
      " A triangle that has 3 equal sides and 3 equal angles is known as ",
    answer: [
      "scalene triangle",
      "isosceles triangle",
      "right angle triangle",
      "equilateral triangle",
    ],
    correct: 3,
    id: 0,
  },

  {
    question: " Area of a triangle with base b and height h is represented by",
    answer: ["1⁄2 × bh", "2 + bh", "2 × bh", "2⁄bh"],
    correct: 0,
    id: 1,
  },

  {
    question: " A triangle with the angle of 90 ° is called ",
    answer: [
      "vertical triangle",
      "supplementary triangle",
      "right angle triangle",
      "reflective triangle",
    ],
    correct: 2,
    id: 2,
  },

  {
    question:
      "A triangle that has 2 equal sides and 2 equal angles is known as ",
    answer: [
      "isosceles triangle",
      "equilateral triangle",
      "scalene triangle",
      "right angle",
    ],
    correct: 0,
    id: 3,
  },

  {
    question:
      " A triangle that has no equal sides and no equal angles is known as",
    answer: [
      "isosceles triangle",
      "scalene triangle",
      "equilateral triangle",
      "right angle",
    ],
    correct: 1,
    id: 4,
  },

  {
    question: " The sum of all the angles in a triangle is ___.",
    answer: ["180 degrees", "270 degrees", "90 degrees", "300 degree"],
    correct: 0,
    id: 5,
  },

  {
    question:
      " If a triangle has sides of 8cm,6cm and 6cm what type of triangle is it?",
    answer: [
      "isosceles triangle",
      "scalene triangle",
      "equilateral triangle",
      "right angle triangle",
    ],
    correct: 0,
    id: 6,
  },

  {
    question: " What type of triangle has angles of 45deg, 90deg, 45deg?",
    answer: [
      "isosceles triangle",
      "scalene triangle",
      "equilateral triangle",
      "right angle triangle",
    ],
    correct: 0,
    id: 7,
  },

  {
    question: "The perimeter of an equilateral triangle of side 12cm is: ",
    answer: ["24cm", "48cm", "36cm", "30cm"],
    correct: 2,
    id: 8,
  },

  {
    question: "What is the longest side of a right angle triangle? ",
    answer: ["Perpendicular", " Hypotenuse", "Base", " None of the above"],
    correct: 1,
    id: 9,
  },
];
export { questionArray };
